so as the title suggests I $900 and it's
less about that amount of money because
that amount of money isn't exactly we're
all changing our life changing but it's
a fun amount to win and the things that
had to happen for me to win that I don't
play the lottery very often I only play
it when I feel the urge because it's at
a high number and it's a high enough
number that I can play with it's for
entertainment value so when I went
grocery shopping on Tuesday the lotto
max was it I don't even know 40 million
I believe and so I bought a ticket with
thinking that I would have until Friday
to be entertained because that's when
Lotto Max does their their draw but the
next day the numbers the amount in the
pool had gone up and I was like all
right it's Tuesday they have the draw
too so I just bought the ticket and now
it's more money and I did want to have
that entertainment so I'm like okay I'm
gonna go buy a ticket by the time by
Friday and on Thursday night my kid had
his sleepover and I had a women's night
out with the people in my community and
she was having to sleep over there and I
forgot to buy I bought her chips when I
went grocery shopping on the Tuesday but
I forgot to bring them because we had a
little bit of drama we were leaving so I
walked to the nearby 7-eleven in order
to buy some plain potato chips which was
that she wanted for the sleepover well I
was there I was like okay I got the
lottery ticket checked for Tuesday and
it wasn't a winner enough for ticket I
was like I kind of want to play with
that number I was having fun I wanted to
play with the amount of money in my head
again so I bought a ticket I was like
would you like the extra like no fifty
million or nothing
I don't and then this morning when I
went to walk the dog after our board
meeting I got the chicken ticket checked
and I thought he said it was like 9:25
it was like cool awesome which is about
the most I think ten dollars the most
I've ever won on the lottery and usually
I just want a free ticket that's like I
was even a little disappointed that I
won down 25 even though you could buy
all those two tickets with that but then
I feel like I could choose to buy a
ticket with that as opposed to when it
gives you a free ticket there's no
option and so I did buy another ticket
for because the number went up again
it's not sixty million I was like
alright well the chances actually said
kind of go down that I'd bought it there
and redeemed it there and even he was
like that's the largest number we've
every one here and then I lost my wallet
there so I just wouldn't picked it up it
was quite but it's like the things that
had to happen I'd if I take it on
Tuesday it had mistakenly forgot my kids
chip bag go there to buy it and then
Valentine's Day I won nine hundred
dollars and now I'm playing with what to
do with that money because there's
something about it run like I want it to
facilitate the scheduling app and
whether that means finding someone who
will volunteer and critics I know you
nine hundred dollars I'd have to pay
somebody in another country to make it
even that it would be low for that for
that that so possibly using it for
servers and for that kind thing but I'm
gonna have a brainstorm with my brother
later as to what to spend it on but I do
want it and we sell it eight the project
there was something about it but I also
just maybe it's just this story that
facilitates it may be the right person
clicks on this video because they're
like oh you know dollars and this
channel has become me telling my story
to see how we create the technology but
these little things that happen like
it's not just winning the nine hundred
dollars like what had to transpire for
me to win not and seen like hey I
wouldn't grocery shopping and if I
hadn't been mistaken about the the
lottery days and if I hadn't forgotten
my kids chips and I walked to the store
and bought it then I wouldn't have this
money to play with in my head and
whoever ends up coming on board because
I mean well they may be paid that money
into the pool for creating the
scheduling app and then everything that
comes out of once we have the scheduling
app is like these things just all
interweave together and I want to share
a tiny piece though with you and I feel
like lottery winnings are more Universal
like more like okay yeah I get it
like that's luck but the things that had
to transpire or also look to be able to
to achieve that share that with you